practicalhacks.com 2018-10-07

# Privacy Policy

At _**Practical Hacks**_ , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by _**Practical Hacks**_ and how it is used.

We require all parties who wish to publish comments on our blog to provide us with their valid email address. We do not release your submitted email address to the public or any third party nor use it for marketing purposes. However, any information you publish via our “reply” tool is made public, so please be careful about what personally identifiable information you publish on our blog.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, Practical Hacks makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

_**Practical Hacks**_ may use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on _**Practical Hacks**_ send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies, such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

_**Practical Hacks**_ has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. _**Practical Hacks**_ ’ blog privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

We reserve the right to engage third party advertising as indicated herein at any time with no further notice to you.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

If you have any questions, please contact me via the form on the **Contact Me** page.
